Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Clover Brook, undated; 16 (Box 1540)
    - [Attic (?) with fireplace and long table at Clover Brook], 6
    - [Sitting room at Clover Brook], 7
    - [Den with fireplace and ski equipment at Clover Brook], 8
    - [Bedroom with photo of Lowell Thomas on the dresser at Clover Brook], 9
  - Subject files: Clover Brook (Provensen event), circa 1927; 17 (Box 1540)
    - [Lowell Thomas and others holding spears in Clover Brook (?)], 1
    - [Four women sitting on the front steps of a home at Clover Brook], 2
    - [People by a diving board at Clover Brook], 3
    - "Cloverbrook", 4
    - Verso: "Cloverbrook", 4-verso
    - Caption: Merry Christmas to Aunt Eunice - Frank and Janet, 5
    - Cloverbrook when L.T. purchased, 6
    - Verso: Cloverbrook when L.T. purchased, 6-verso
    - [Inground swimming pool at Cloverbrook], 7
    - [Beautiful landscapping at Cloverbrook], 8
    - [Driveway leading to Cloverbrook], 9
    - [Backyard at Cloverbrook], 10
    - [Stairs leading to swimming pool at Cloverbrook], 11
    - [Path through the trees at Cloverbrook], 12
  - Subject files: Coal mining (Virginia), circa 1920 - 1930; 18 (Box 1540)
    - V1-4 "knuckles down" at recess, at school for colored children in mining camp at Raleigh, W. Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 1
    - Verso: V1-4 "knuckles down" at recess, at school for colored children in mining camp at Raleigh, W. Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 1-verso
    - V1-5 The champion rolls a wicked miggie at recess, colored school at mining camp. Raleigh, W. Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 2
    - Verso: V1-5 The champion rolls a wicked miggie at recess, colored school at mining camp. Raleigh, W. Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 2-verso
    - V1-6 Coal conveyer and tipple at Black Knight #3, Raleigh, W. Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 3
    - Verso: V1-6 Coal conveyer and tipple at Black Knight #3, Raleigh, W. Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 3-verso
    - V1-8 Electric locomotive "Pulling a trip" from Black Knight #3 mine, Raleigh, W. Va Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 4
    - Verso: V1-8 Electric locomotive "Pulling a trip" from Black Knight #3 mine, Raleigh, W. Va Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 4-verso
    - V2-9 Up the Holler at Slab Fork, W. Va. Showing tipple, cabins and colored church Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 5
    - Verso: V2-9 Up the Holler at Slab Fork, W. Va. Showing tipple, cabins and colored church Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 5-verso
    - Sunset over "Spook Mountain" overlooking the mining camp at Slab Fork, W. Va.; Note: Two little colored boys talking one day at Slab Fork, W. Va. One pointed across the "holler." "See that there moun-tin" he asked his companion. "Dat's Spook Moun-tain", "Why you call dat Spook Moun-tin?", "Cause'n I know a man went up thar one day, ad' he sayed, "Spook, cum git my wife." An when dat man went home his wide was jus' as daid as a dwag." After a moment's silence the little fellow continued, I bet iff'n you went over there an' say "Spook, cum git me," we never would see hide or hair of you again.......I bet there ain't a man in the whole Slab Fork 'ud dare go up that moun-tin and holler "Here Spook!", 6
    - Verso: V2-10 Sunset over "Spook Mountain" overlooking the mining camp at Slab Fork, W. Va.; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 6-verso
    - Note: [with 18.6] V2-10 Two little colored boys talking one day at Slab Fork, W. Va. One pointed across the "holler." "See that there moun-tin" he asked his companion. "Dat's Spook Moun-tain", "Why you call dat Spook Moun-tin?", "Cause'n I know a man went up thar one day, ad' he sayed, "Spook, cum git my wife." An when dat man went home his wide was jus' as daid as a dwag." After a moment's silence the little fellow continued, I bet iff'n you went over there an' say "Spook, cum git me," we never would see hide or hair of you again.......I bet there ain't a man in the whole Slab Fork 'ud dare go up that moun-tin and holler "Here Spook!", 7
    - V3-2 Miner's houses, tipple and slack pile at Summerlee, W. Va. New River Company; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 8
    - Verso: V3-2 Miner's houses, tipple and slack pile at Summerlee, W. Va. New River Company; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 8-verso
    - V3-8 PAY DAY AT RALIEGH COAL AND COKE COMPANY, Raleigh, W. Va. Miners' cars parked at the pay office; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 9
    - Verso: V3-8 PAY DAY AT RALIEGH COAL AND COKE COMPANY, Raleigh, W. Va. Miners' cars parked at the pay office; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 9-verso
    - V3-9 Coal miners and their wives filing toward the paymaster's office and their semi-monthly envelope. Raleigh, W. Va.; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 10
    - Verso: V3-9 Coal miners and their wives filing toward the paymaster's office and their semi-monthly envelope. Raleigh, W. Va.; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 10-verso
    - V3-11 ALL DRESSED UP FOR PAY DAY; Coal miners in line and about to get their pay envelopes at Raleigh, W. Va.; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 11
    - Verso: V3-11 ALL DRESSED UP FOR PAY DAY; Coal miners in line and about to get their pay envelopes at Raleigh, W. Va.; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 11-verso
    - V3-12 Pay day brings the miners and their families to the company store at Raleigh, W. Va. For business as well as to swap the news; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 12
    - Verso: V3-12 Pay day brings the miners and their families to the company store at Raleigh, W. Va. For business as well as to swap the news; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 12-verso
    - V5-7 Executive staff of Frontier Nursing Service at Headquarters, Wendover, Ky. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 13
    - Verso: V5-7 Executive staff of Frontier Nursing Service at Headquarters, Wendover, Ky. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 13-verso
    - V5-8 Miss Betty Lester, R.N. Midwifery Supervisor, Frontier Nursing Service, in summer uniform and Miss Mary B. Willeford, R.N., Assistant Director of Field Work, F.N.S. in winter uniform at Wendover, Ky.; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 14
    - Verso: V5-8 Miss Betty Lester, R.N. Midwifery Supervisor, Frontier Nursing Service, in summer uniform and Miss Mary B. Willeford, R.N., Assistant Director of Field Work, F.N.S. in winter uniform at Wendover, Ky.; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 14-verso
    - V5-9 Early morning shift ready to go into mine at Jenkins, Ky. Mine #206 Consolidated Coal Co. Note dinner pails and open-flame lamps. (picture taken 6.30 a.m.); Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 15
    - Verso: V5-9 Early morning shift ready to go into mine at Jenkins, Ky. Mine #206 Consolidated Coal Co. Note dinner pails and open-flame lamps. (picture taken 6.30 a.m.); Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 15-verso
    - V6-8 Shantytown still clings to the hillside after the mine has been worked out and abandoned. Squatters drift in and make them nests of vicious squalor; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 16
    - Verso: V6-8 Shantytown still clings to the hillside after the mine has been worked out and abandoned. Squatters drift in and make them nests of vicious squalor; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 16-verso
    - V6-10 Miners' houses along the main street of Amonate, Va. Pocahontas Fuel Corporation. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 17
    - Verso: V6-10 Miners' houses along the main street of Amonate, Va. Pocahontas Fuel Corporation. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 17-verso
    - V6-12 A Two-Job Man; Clarence Peacock, coal miner at Boissevain, Va, has bought his own farm and house with the help of the company. A 7-hour mining day, with Saturdays and Sundays free leaves him time enough for farming; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 18
    - Verso: V6-12 A Two-Job Man; Clarence Peacock, coal miner at Boissevain, Va, has bought his own farm and house with the help of the company. A 7-hour mining day, with Saturdays and Sundays free leaves him time enough for farming; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 18-verso
    - V7-5 Hauling timber into original Pocahontas #1 Mine. Julian Levay, engineer is one of the best call players and is catcher on the Pocahontas team; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 19
    - Verso: V7-5 Hauling timber into original Pocahontas #1 Mine. Julian Levay, engineer is one of the best call players and is catcher on the Pocahontas team; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 19-verso
    - V8-8 the Miners of To-Morrow Discuss Weighty Problems; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 20
    - Verso: V8-8 the Miners of To-Morrow Discuss Weighty Problems; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 20-verso
    - V9-3 Dan Lasca, miner, takes his Sunday ease at his cabin near Mine #20 Island Creek Coal Co. Holden, W. Va.; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 21
    - Verso: V9-3 Dan Lasca, miner, takes his Sunday ease at his cabin near Mine #20 Island Creek Coal Co. Holden, W. Va.; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 21-verso
    - V9-5 110,000 tons of coal in storage. Island Creek Coal Co. Holden, W. Va. It would take 20 trains of 100 cars each to move this pile; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 22
    - Verso: V9-5 110,000 tons of coal in storage. Island Creek Coal Co. Holden, W. Va. It would take 20 trains of 100 cars each to move this pile; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 22-verso
    - V9-6 Apparently no hillside is too steep for a miner to cultivate in Kentucky Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 23
    - Verso: V9-6 Apparently no hillside is too steep for a miner to cultivate in Kentucky Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 23-verso
  - Subject files: Coal mining (Virginia), circa 1920 - 1930; 19 (Box 1540)
    - V9-7 Most any mode of travel goes in the mining district of Kentucky; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 1
    - Verso: V9-7 Most any mode of travel goes in the mining district of Kentucky; Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 1-verso
    - V10-2 Homstead [sic] of "Bad" John Wright, near Jenkins, Kentucky, said to be prototype of "Jud Tolliver" of Fox's book, "The Trail of the Lonesome Pine." Wright, a giant pioneer and notorious killer was said to have fought on both sides during the Civil War. Having had 12 "wives" he got religion, was baptized and married his last wife. At one time he had 3 "wives" living within 10 miles of each other. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 2
    - Verso: V10-2 Homstead [sic] of "Bad" John Wright, near Jenkins, Kentucky, said to be prototype of "Jud Tolliver" of Fox's book, "The Trail of the Lonesome Pine." Wright, a giant pioneer and notorious killer was said to have fought on both sides during the Civil War. Having had 12 "wives" he got religion, was baptized and married his last wife. At one time he had 3 "wives" living within 10 miles of each other. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 2-verso
    - V10-4 Miners' cottages and their hillside farms at Fleming, Ky. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 3
    - Verso: V10-4 Miners' cottages and their hillside farms at Fleming, Ky. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 3-verso
    - 10-5 Couriers, Misses Elizabeth Duval and Jean Hollins of NY, have charge of the nurses'horses, and are themselves mounted messengers. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 4
    - Verso: V10-5 Couriers, Misses Elizabeth Duval and Jean Hollins of NY, have charge of the nurses'horses, and are themselves mounted messengers. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 4-verso
    - V10-6 Miss Dorothy Buck, R.N., of the Frontier Nursing Service of Kentucky leaving headquarters at Wendover, KY with 40-lb saddlebags, packed with midwifery kit, snakebite antitoxin, and vaccine and inoculations against smallpox, diphtheria and typhoid. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 5
    - Verso: V10-6 Miss Dorothy Buck, R.N., of the Frontier Nursing Service of Kentucky leaving headquarters at Wendover, KY with 40-lb saddlebags, packed with midwifery kit, snakebite antitoxin, and vaccine and inoculations against smallpox, diphtheria and typhoid. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 5-verso
    - V10-11 A stream in "tide" doesn't keep Miss Dorothy Buck R.N. of the Frontier Nursing Service of Kentucky from reaching an expectant mother in a distant mountain cabin. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 6
    - Verso: V10-11 A stream in "tide" doesn't keep Miss Dorothy Buck R.N. of the Frontier Nursing Service of Kentucky from reaching an expectant mother in a distant mountain cabin. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 6-verso
    - V10-12 Miss Dorothy Buck, R.N. of the Frontier Nursing Service of Kentucky leaves the headquarters at Wendover in answer to a hurry call from a mountain cabin. Day or night babies or shootins [sic] may summon her "up the holler." Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 7
    - Verso: V10-12 Miss Dorothy Buck, R.N. of the Frontier Nursing Service of Kentucky leaves the headquarters at Wendover in answer to a hurry call from a mountain cabin. Day or night babies or shootins [sic] may summon her "up the holler." Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 7-verso
    - V11-1 Kentucky farmer plowing steep hillside for corn planting. Wendover, Ky. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 8
    - Verso: V11-1 Kentucky farmer plowing steep hillside for corn planting. Wendover, Ky. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 8-verso
    - V11-3 The soil is mighty "pore" but this is where a Kentucky mountaineer raises the year's food supply for his family. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 9
    - Verso: V11-3 The soil is mighty "pore" but this is where a Kentucky mountaineer raises the year's food supply for his family. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 9-verso
    - V11-5 Miss Betty Lester, R.N., Supervisor of Midwifery, Frontier Nursing Service of Kentucky. Her saddle bags carry complete midwifery kit, and she is ready to race the stork up the rocky creeks to lonely cabins. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 10
    - Verso: V11-5 Miss Betty Lester, R.N., Supervisor of Midwifery, Frontier Nursing Service of Kentucky. Her saddle bags carry complete midwifery kit, and she is ready to race the stork up the rocky creeks to lonely cabins. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 10-verso
    - V11-9 Miss Betty Lester, R.N., supervisor of Midwifery, Frontier Nursing Service visits a mountain family in her district, to see that "all's well." Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 11
    - Verso: V11-9 Miss Betty Lester, R.N., supervisor of Midwifery, Frontier Nursing Service visits a mountain family in her district, to see that "all's well." Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 11-verso
    - V11-11 Geraldine and Guy, healthy Kentucky mountain children lured from hiding by promise of a stick of gum. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 12
    - Verso: V11-11 Geraldine and Guy, healthy Kentucky mountain children lured from hiding by promise of a stick of gum. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 12-verso
    - V11-12 Gerald and John Henry (baby) Brock, at the door of their cabin on Hurricane, Mt. Kentucky are prize exhibits of the Frontier Nursing Service. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 13
    - Verso: V11-12 Gerald and John Henry (baby) Brock, at the door of their cabin on Hurricane, Mt. Kentucky are prize exhibits of the Frontier Nursing Service. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 13-verso
    - V13-1 Part of the main highway between Hyden, Ky. and Wendover, headquarters of the Frontier Nursing Service. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 14
    - Verso: V13-1 Part of the main highway between Hyden, Ky. and Wendover, headquarters of the Frontier Nursing Service. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 14-verso
    - V13-2 Courier of Frontier Nursing Service guides a "brought on woman" (stranger) to headquarters of the Service at Wendover, Ky. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 15
    - Verso: V13-2 Courier of Frontier Nursing Service guides a "brought on woman" (stranger) to headquarters of the Service at Wendover, Ky. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 15-verso
    - V13-4 Mist hangs over Powell's valley in the Allegheny coal region of Virginia, seen from Daniel Boone's trail on Stone Mountain, near Norton, Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 16
    - Verso: V13-4 Mist hangs over Powell's valley in the Allegheny coal region of Virginia, seen from Daniel Boone's trail on Stone Mountain, near Norton, Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 16-verso
    - V13-3 Many a property owner in the Kentucky mountains digs his winter coal from his own back yard. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 17
    - Verso: V13-3 Many a property owner in the Kentucky mountains digs his winter coal from his own back yard. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 17-verso
    - V13-5 A typical mountain farm in Virginia such as many of the miners come from. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 18
    - Verso: V13-5 A typical mountain farm in Virginia such as many of the miners come from. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 18-verso
    - V13-7 125-year-old log cabin, typical of those built by pioneers in the Allegheny mountains of Virginia, long before coal was discovered in this region. Near Norton, Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 19
    - Verso: V13-7 125-year-old log cabin, typical of those built by pioneers in the Allegheny mountains of Virginia, long before coal was discovered in this region. Near Norton, Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 19-verso
    - V13-10 G. P. W. Black, Assistant Superintendent of Stonega Coal & Coke Co. Derby, Virginia, standing in front of coal seam at outcrop. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 20
    - Verso: V13-10 G. P. W. Black, Assistant Superintendent of Stonega Coal & Coke Co. Derby, Virginia, standing in front of coal seam at outcrop. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 20-verso
    - V13-11 Coal miners of Stonega Coal & Coke Co, Derby, Virginia, live in tile houses equipped with electricity and running water Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 21
    - Verso: V13-11 Coal miners of Stonega Coal & Coke Co, Derby, Virginia, live in tile houses equipped with electricity and running water Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 21-verso
    - V14-3 T. J. Berry, aged 74. Says he is "oldest Republican in Virginia." Miner, preacher, politician, and entertainer. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 22
    - Verso: V14-3 T. J. Berry, aged 74. Says he is "oldest Republican in Virginia." Miner, preacher, politician, and entertainer. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 22-verso
    - V14-4 A typical group of miners' children. At Derby, Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 23
    - Verso: V14-4 A typical group of miners' children. At Derby, Va. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 23-verso
    - V15-8 Aerial tramway to slate dump at Stonega Coal & Coke Co. Derby, Va. Spontaneous combustion of the volatile materials cause these dumps to burn and smoke continuously Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 24
    - Verso: V15-8 Aerial tramway to slate dump at Stonega Coal & Coke Co. Derby, Va. Spontaneous combustion of the volatile materials cause these dumps to burn and smoke continuously Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 24-verso
    - V15-9 Looking out of Natural Tunnel, Virginia. The tunnell [sic] is nearly 1000 ft long, 100ft high through which runs Stock Creek. The Cliff walls at the tunnell [sic] entrance are over 400 ft high. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 25
    - Verso: V15-9 Looking out of Natural Tunnel, Virginia. The tunnell [sic] is nearly 1000 ft long, 100ft high through which runs Stock Creek. The Cliff walls at the tunnell [sic] entrance are over 400 ft high. Photograph by R.W. Barton, Pelham Manor, N.Y., 25-verso
    - Drilling the Coal Preparatory to Shooting; Current for the electrical drills is brought by a reel-type engine from the trolly [sic] wire in the main drift. J.H. Edwards, Electrical Engineer, Associate Editor, Coal Age, 2962 Winters Road-Huntington, W. VA, The Film Shop, Enamel, Jan 31 1930, Tone, Huntington, W. VA, 26
    - Verso: Drilling the Coal Preparatory to Shooting; Current for the electrical drills is brought by a reel-type engine from the trolly [sic] wire in the main drift. J.H. Edwards, Electrical Engineer, Associate Editor, Coal Age, 2962 Winters Road-Huntington, W. VA, The Film Shop, Enamel, Jan 31 1930, Tone, Huntington, W. VA, 26-verso
    - A Cutter at Work; Bits on an endless chain cut a " kerf" at the bottom of the coal seam, before drilling and shooting down the coal take place. Fine particles of coal dust produced by the cutter are called "bug dust". J.H. Edwards, Electrical Engineer, Associate Editor, Coal Age, 2962 Winters Road-Huntington, W. VA, The Film Shop, Enamel, Jan 31 1930, Tone, Huntington, W. VA, 27
    - Verso: A Cutter at Work; Bits on an endless chain cut a " kerf" at the bottom of the coal seam, before drilling and shooting down the coal take place. Fine particles of coal dust produced by the cutter are called "bug dust". J.H. Edwards, Electrical Engineer, Associate Editor, Coal Age, 2962 Winters Road-Huntington, W. VA, The Film Shop, Enamel, Jan 31 1930, Tone, Huntington, W. VA, 27-verso
    - Pulling a Trip Underground; Distance from working face to mine mouth may be five miles. J.H. Edwards, Electrical Engineer, Associate Editor, Coal Age, 2962 Winters Road-Huntington, W. VA, The Film Shop, Enamel, Jan 31 1930, Tone, Huntington, W. VA, 28
    - Verso: Pulling a Trip Underground; Distance from working face to mine mouth may be five miles. J.H. Edwards, Electrical Engineer, Associate Editor, Coal Age, 2962 Winters Road-Huntington, W. VA, The Film Shop, Enamel, Jan 31 1930, Tone, Huntington, W. VA, 28-verso
    - [Coal miners sitting on some type of rail vehicle], 29
  - Subject files: Jacqueline Cochran, undated; 20 (Box 1540)
    - Jacqueline Cochran, famous American woman flier (ferried bombers WWII), married to Floyd Odlum - Atlas Corp., 1
    - Note: Jacqueline Cochran, famous American woman flier (ferried bombers WWII), married to Floyd Odlum - Atlas Corp., 2
    - [unidentified pilot], 3
    - [unidentified men in uniform], 4
  - Subject files: Roy Cohn, 1970; 21 (Box 1540)
    - Roy Cohn, M[?], L.T., Khatmandu [sic], Apr 1970, 1
    - Verso: Roy Cohn, M[?], L.T., Khatmandu [sic], Apr 1970, 1-verso
    - [Roy Cohn and Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [unidentified man and Lowell Thomas], 3
  - Subject files: Colleges, 1949 - 1974; 22 (Box 1540)
    - LT, Pres. A.G. Heugli, Ray S[?], 1
    - Verso: LT, Pres. A.G. Heugli, Ray S[?], 1-verso
    - Caption: Valparaiso University, 100th Commencement, May 19, 1974, 2
    - Univ. of the Pacific-Alaska. (formerly Alaska Methodist), 3
    - Verso: Univ. of the Pacific-Alaska. (formerly Alaska Methodist), 3-verso